<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sound Alert App</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>

    <string-array name="db_explain_arr">
        <item>  0dB: The softest sound a human can hear.</item>
        <item> 10dB: Normal breathing, rustling of fallen leaves.</item>
        <item> 20dB: Whispering from 1 meter away, rural night.</item>
        <item> 30dB: Quiet library, soft conversation.</item>
        <item> 40dB: Quiet office, bedroom away from road noise.</item>
        <item> 50dB: Light traffic up close, refrigerator, light breeze.</item>
        <item> 60dB: Loud indoor conversation, teacher\'s lecture.</item>
        <item> 70dB: Busy traffic, noisy restaurant.</item>
        <item> 80dB: Bustling street, alarm clock ringing, noisy factory.</item>
        <item> 90dB: Noisy bar, bulldozer, snowmobile noise.</item>
        <item>100dB: Tractor startup, pneumatic drill sound.</item>
        <item>110dB: Rock music, crying of a child.</item>
        <item>120dB: Threshold of discomfort, thunder sound.</item>
        <item>130dB: Jet engine sound within 30 meters.</item>
        <item>180dB: Spacecraft launch.</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- 听力等级 -->
    <string-array name="hearing_rank_arr">
        <item>Normal</item>
        <item>Minor</item>
        <item>Medium</item>
        <item>Medium to Serious</item>
        <item>Serious</item>
        <item>Very Serious</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- 分析与建议 -->
    <string-array name="propose_arr">
        <item>Normal hearing ability：\n\t\t  Normal hearing ability, keep up the good work.</item>
        <item>Minor hearing loss：\n\t\t  It is not particularly good for you to hear low voices in a noisy environment, but there is no problem with daily communication. Do not worry too much, do not expose yourself to noise for long periods of time, and do not wear headphones for long periods of time.</item>
        <item>Medium hearing loss：\n\t\t  There is no problem with your daily communication, but your communication over long distances and in noisy environments is not ideal. It is recommended to go to the hospital for a detailed further examination.</item>
        <item>Medium to Serious hearing loss：\n\t\t  There is no problem with your daily communication, but your communication over long distances and in noisy environments is not ideal. It is recommended to go to the hospital for a detailed further examination.</item>
        <item>Serious hearing loss：\n\t\t  You can still communicate one-on-one, but daily communication is somewhat difficult and requires the speaker to speak at a higher volume, which will affect your quality of life. It is recommended that you go to the hospital for further examination or to a hearing aid store for a consultation.</item>
        <item>Very serious hearing loss：\n\t\t  You seldom participate in daily life communication, and you feel that other people\'s voices are muted. Your current hearing loss seriously affects your quality of life. You need to go to the hospital for further examination as soon as possible or go to a hearing aid store for consultation.</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- 检查设备 -->
    <string name="check_device_des1">1. Please wear a headphone, click "Test" button, to test your headphone.</string>
    <string name="check_device_des2">2. If Left Ear and Right Ear is working, then choose the ear that has optimal hearing to test.</string>
    <!-- 检查设备 -->

    <string name="introduceText1">\n This application is used to detect sound noises and trigger alerts if classified as potentially dangerous.</string>
    <string name="introduceText2">\n The sound alert system app can help alert you of dangers when distracted. </string>
    <string name="end">Minor hearing loss：26-40dB\nMedium hearing loss：41-55dB\nMedium to Serious hearing loss：56-70dB\nSerious hearing loss：71-90dB\nVery serious hearing loss：>91dB</string>
</resources>
